The best is yet to come.
The Last Movie Star is a drama film directed by Adam Rifkin.
An aging screen icon gets lured into accepting an award at a rinky-dink film festival in Nashville, Tenn., sending
him on a hilarious fish-out-of-water adventure and an unexpectedly poignant journey into his past.
Vic Edwards, played by Burt Reynolds.
Lil McDougal, played by Ariel Winter.
Sonny, played by Chevy Chase.
Doug McDougal, played by Clark Duke.
Shane McAvoy, played by Ellar Coltrane.
Faith Cole, played by Nikki Blonsky.
The Last Movie Star is a 2017 American comedy-drama film written and directed by Adam Rifkin, and
starring Burt Reynolds, Ariel Winter, Clark Duke, Ellar Coltrane and Chevy Chase.
The film premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival on April 22, 2017.
It was released through DirecTV Cinema on February 22, 2018, before being released in a
limited release and through video on demand on March 30, 2018 by A24.
The film explores themes of nostalgia, old man, hollywood, nashville, tennessee.
The tone is emotional.